<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio website for Aris Georgakopoulos</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Portfolio website for Aris Georgakopoulos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/blogs/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/about/</guid>
      <description>I am currently reading for my Masters in Financial Analysis at London Business School. Prior to that I completed my undergraduate degree in Accounting &amp;amp; Finance at Athens University of Economics and Business.
I am passionate about the markets and find very exciting the analysis and integration of world economic and geopolitical events in potential trading ideas and algorithms.
In my free time I like to take salsa dancing lessons and go to salsa parties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong AirBnb Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/projects/hong_kong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/hong_kong/</guid>
      <description>This report contains a detailed analysis of the AirBnb market across Hong Kong. We begin by conducting Exploratory Data Analysis and visualize some key findings from our dataset. Next, we visualize the distribution of AirBnB rentals across the city using Mapping. Subsequently, we try to come up with a Regression Model that predicts the average cost for a four night stay for 2 people in Hong Kong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ipsum</title>
      <link>/blogs/ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/ipsum/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matlab</title>
      <link>/blogs/matlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/matlab/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/blogs/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/resume/</guid>
      <description>EDUCATION 2020 - 2021 London Business School Masters in Financial Analysis
Relevant coursework: Fixed Income Securities, Financial Engineering &amp;amp; Risk Management, Time Series Analysis, Credit Risk, Data Analytics in R
2014 - 2019 Athens University of Economics and Business BSc Accounting &amp;amp; Finance
Relevant coursework: Market Micro-structure, Computational Finance, Risk Management, Econometrics, Fixed Income, Derivatives, Portfolio Analysis
Academic projects: Portfolio Analysis and CVaR Optimization, Variation of Glosten - Milgrom model, Constant Proportion Portfolio Insurance</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars)## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
